Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Beehive, 152828
  - Subseries B: Technical notations and lab related paperwork, 152883
    - 135.0087A-135.0091A. Photo and envelope, 1985; 152890 (Box 23, Folder 926)
    - 135.0042A-135.0093A. Music cue sheets, note., undated; 152889 (Box 23, Folder 927)
    - 135.0094A-135.0098A. 2 letters., undated; 152888 (Box 23, Folder 928)
    - 135.0130A-135.0132A. Timing sheet, timing strip, 1985; 152887 (Box 23, Folder 929)
    - 135.0151A. Timing record, undated; 152886 (Box 23, Folder 930)
    - 135.0163A-135.0134A Printing and Negative Cleaning report, color filter, instructions to timer., undated; 152885 (Box 23, Folder 930A)
    - 135.0165A Printing and Negative Cleaning report, Packing slip, undated; 152884 (Box 23, Folder 930B)
  - Subseries C: Production Materials, Film, 152863
    - Agreement between Jim Self and Frank Moore, undated; 152882 (Box 23, Folder 931)
    - Bee Quiz, undated; 152881 (Box 23, Folder 932)
    - "Curse of Isadora" New York Times article from November 23, 198x. Used as source material for Beehive, ca. 1980; 152880 (Box 23, Folder 933)
    - Fundraising and Budget, 1982-1986; 152879 (Box 23, Folder 934)
    - Invoices, 1987; 152878 (Box 23, Folder 935)
    - Letter Re: Ellen van Schuylenburch, 1982; 152877 (Box 23, Folder 936)
    - Letter from Frank Moore to Jean, 1985; 152876 (Box 23, Folder 937)
    - Letterhead, undated; 152875 (Box 23, Folder 938)
    - Lighting parameters, undated; 152874 (Box 23, Folder 939)
    - Maeterlinck, Maurice. "La Vie Des Abeilles" approximate translation of paragraph from French to English, undated; 152873 (Box 23, Folder 940)
    - Miscellaneous papers and drawings, undated; 152872 (Box 23, Folder 941)
    - Notepad with dimensions, drawings and to do lists for costumes, undated; 152871 (Box 23, Folder 942)
    - Primary Performance Group balance sheet and auditor's report. June 30, 1985, 152870 (Box 23, Folder 943)
    - Beehive Production Schedule Memo, 1986; 152869 (Box 23, Folder 944)
    - Beehive set instructions, undated; 152868 (Box 23, Folder 945)
    - Source Materials, 152867 (Box 23, Folder 946)
    - Special Thanks credits, undated; 152866 (Box 23, Folder 947)
    - Storyboard, undated; 152865 (Box 23, Folder 948)
    - To do lists, undated; 152864 (Box 23, Folder 949)
  - Subseries D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theatre Production, 152847
    - Aggreements between Frank Moore, Scott Johnson and Jim Self. For "Beehive" ballet performance in Boston. February 7., undated; 152862 (Box 23, Folder 950)
    - Boston Ballet Company, 1987; 152861 (Box 23, Folder 951)
    - Beehive Correspondence with Angiers, 1985-1986; 152860 (Box 23, Folder 952)
    - Beehive correspondence with Boston, 1985-1986; 152859 (Box 23, Folder 953)
    - Costume lists, Angiers to Boston, undated; 152858 (Box 23, Folder 954)
    - Encouragement for Beehive, Boston, undated; 152857 (Box 23, Folder 955)
    - Lighting Parameters, 152856 (Box 23, Folder 956)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199064 (Box 23, Folder 957)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199065 (Box 23, Folder 958)
    - Modified Rep. Hanging plot. Boston Ballet, 1987; 152855 (Box 23, Folder 959)
    - Performance Schedule, Beehove 1986-1987, 152854 (Box 23, Folder 960)
    - Production bidsheet, Boston Ballet., 1987; 152853 (Box 23, Folder 961)
    - Projector information, sent by Boston Ballet to Frank Moore, 1986; 152852 (Box 23, Folder 962)
    - Receipts and financial information, 1983-1986; 152851 (Box 23, Folder 963)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, undated; 152850 (Box 23, Folder 964)
    - Scott Johnson, technical requirements, undated; 152849 (Box 23, Folder 965)
    - "Special Note Regarding the Development of Beehive", undated; 152848 (Box 23, Folder 966)
  - Subseries E: Promotional Materials, 152838
    - Invitation postcard to Beehive at CNCD d'Angers, 1985; 152846 (Box 23, Folder 967)
    - Invitations to Beehive at Theatre Municipal D'Angers, undated; 152845 (Box 23, Folder 968)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199060 (Box 23, Folder 969)
    - Program from French Production at Centre National de Danse Contemporaine D'Angers, 1985; 152844 (Box 23, Folder 970)
    - Boston Ballet newspaper clippings, undated; 152843 (Box 23, Folder 971)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199061 (Box 23, Folder 972)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199062 (Box 23, Folder 973)
    - Boston Ballet Theatre bills, 1986; 152842 (Box 23, Folder 974)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199063 (Box 23, Folder 975)
    - Dance on Camera festival, 1987; 152841 (Box 23, Folder 976)
    - "Awards given in Dance" clipping regarding New York Dance and Performance Awards, undated; 152840 (Box 23, Folder 977)
    - Photographs, undated; 152839 (Box 24, Folder data_value_missing_faa07fa845165a7a2dab216fd08aa95a)
  - Subseries F: Artifacts, 152834
    - Glass Panels, undated; 152837 (Box 23, Folder 978)
    - Lighting scrims and foil material, undated; 152836 (Box 23, Folder 979)
    - Model Flowers, undated; 152835 (Box 23, Folder 980)
    - Item removed to oversize, 199059 (Box 23, Folder 981)
  - Subseries G: Video Recordings - Access Copies, 152832
    Scope and Contents
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Beehive (2005 Restoration), 1985; ID: 135.0274; 152833 (Case 135.0274)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:15:38
      Original Format: 16mm film
    - Beehive, 1985; ID: 135.0287; 255051 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 135.0287)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      TRT: 00:16:00
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
      Source ID: 135.0160
    - Beehive (1985 Dub), ID: 135.0288; 255052 (Case 135.0288, Case 135.0287)
      Original Format: VHS
      Source ID: 135.0158
    - Beehive: Cornell Rough Rehearsal, 1991; ID: 135.0278; 213973 (Case 135.0278)
      TRT: 00:36:00
      Source ID: 135.0157
    - Beehive-- Ballet Excerpts, undated; ID: 135.0279; 213976 (Case 135.0279)
      Physical Characeteristics and Technical Requirements note
      TRT: 00:09:20
      Source ID: 135.0159
    - Beehive Excerpts, 1985 Angers Production, Dub by Frank Moore (Box Digitized Access Files, File 135.0156)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Source Format: VHS, Source ID: 135.0156, Duration: 18 min.
    - Primary Performance Group, Inc., "Beehive Ballet" (Box Digitized Access Files, File 135.0159)
      Source Format: VHS, Source ID: 135.0159, Duration: 9 min.
  - Subseries H: Film - Access Copies, 152829
    Conditions Governing Access
    - "Beehive" (unrestored answer print), 1985; 152830 (Reel 135.0277)
      Physical Charateristics and Technical Requirements note
      Format: 16mm
      Total Footage: 587 ft.
- Series VI: Miller's Wife, 152720
  This series contains all production elements and materials relating to "The Miller's Wife" including film, video and audio elements, production notes, budgets, rental information, production and promotional materials as well as artifacts. Subseries A contains all production elements relating to the film. Items are organized by unique object identifcation numbers. Materials in Subseries B: Technical notations and Lab related paperwork relate to specific reels of film and are organized by unique object idenfication numbers. All other subseries are arrange alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Production Elements, 152819
    - Film Production Elements: 16mm b/w negative and 16mm color positive, 1987-1988; 152827 (Box 135.0133-135.0134)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988; 152826 (Box 135.0136-135.0138)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988; 152825 (Box ID: 135.0179)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988; 152824 (Box 135.0181-135.0254)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988; 152823 (Box 135.0258-135.0260)
    - Video Production Element: Video Story Board #1, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0167; 184576 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0167)
      Video Recording, [20:00], JVC TC-20 SHG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Video Story Board #2, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0166; 152822 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0166)
      Video Recording, [20:00] TDK TC-20 HDX Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Dailies 10/22/87, ID: 135.0168; 184577 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0168)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Kodak Eastman EK T-60 HG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" -- 24" Silent Work Print, [undated]; ID: 135.0169; 184578 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0169)
      Video Recording, [30:00], Eastman Kodak EK T-30 HG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: VHS Master "The Miller's Wife" with Scratchtrack, [undated]; ID: 135.0170; 184579 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0170)
      Video Recording, Maxell EX 120 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: DAT 1 Transfer "The Miller's Wife" 12/27/88, ID: 135.0175; 184584 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0175)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Ampex 197 BCA-60 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: DAT 2 Transfer 12/27/88, ID: 135.0171; 184580 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0171)
      Video Recording, [10:00] Sony KCS-10XBR Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Master of Rough Cut "The Miller's Wife", [undated]; ID: 135.0172; 184581 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0172)
      Video Recording, [24:00], Eastman Kodak EK30 KCA Proffessional EP-930 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Scratchtrack Master "The Miller's Wife" Rough Cut Dub - Silent, [undated]; ID: 135.0173; 184582 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0173)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Eastman Kodak EK30 KCA Proffessional EP-930 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Window Dub "Miller's Wife" - A. Leroy Dialogue - Sound EFX, [undated]; ID: 135.0174; 184583 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0174)
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" Dub, [undated]; ID: 135.0176; 184585 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0176)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Sony Videogenix Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" (Work in Progress) Transfer from 16mm Workprint, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0255; 152821 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0255)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Sony KCA-60XBR Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "Miller's Wife" Work Sample 6/4/90, ID: 135.0256; 184586 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0256)
      Video Recording, [03:00], Sony Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "Miller's Wife" Work Sample 6/4/90, ID: 135.0257; 184587 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0257)
      Video Recording, [03:00], TS-15-S Video Cassette
    - Audio Production Elements: 1/4" reel to reel, 1988-1990; 152820 (Box 23C, Folder ID: 135.0177-135.0178)
  - Subseries B: Technical Notations and Lab Related Paperwork, 152767
    - 135.0169A Dialogue, undated; 152818 (Box 23, Folder 982)
    - 135.0175A Audio log, undated; 152817 (Box 23, Folder 983)
    - 135.0177A Tape log, undated; 152816 (Box 23, Folder 984)
    - 135.0178A tape log, undated; 152815 (Box 23, Folder 985)
    - 135.0179A timing strip, work order, purchase order, printing and cleaning report, labels, 1987; 152814 (Box 23, Folder 986)
    - 135.0180A Timing strip, work order, order form, printing and cleaning report, 1987; 152813 (Box 23, Folder 987)
    - 135.0183A work order, timing strip, P.O., camera report, negative cleaning report, lab order, timer's listing, 1987; 152812 (Box 23, Folder 988)
    - 135.0184A Timing strip, work order, P.O., Negative printing and cleaning report, 1987; 152811 (Box 23, Folder 989)
    - 135.0185A Printing and negative cleaning report, edge number notes, 1987; 152810 (Box 23, Folder 990)
    - 135.0186A, timing strip, work order, P.O., printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152809 (Box 23, Folder 991)
    - 135.0187A, printing and negative cleaning report, timing strip, timer's listing and misc. papers, 1987; 152808 (Box 23, Folder 992)
    - 135.0188A, timing strip, work order, p.o., printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152807 (Box 23, Folder 993)
    - 135.0190A, timing strip, work order, customer order form, timing strip, printing and cleaning report, 1987; 152806 (Box 23, Folder 994)
    - 135.0191A, Edge number note, undated; 152805 (Box 23, Folder 995)
    - 135.0191A-135.0194A, Printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152804 (Box 23, Folder 996)
    - 135.0192, Edge number note, undated; 152803 (Box 23, Folder 997)
    - 135.0193A Edge number note, undated; 152802 (Box 23, Folder 998)
    - 135.0193A Edge number note, undated; 152801 (Box 23, Folder 999)
    - 135.0194A, Edge number note, undated; 152800 (Box 23, Folder 1000)
    - 135.0195A, Edge number note, undated; 152799 (Box 23, Folder 1001)
    - 135.0195A-135.0198A Printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152798 (Box 23, Folder 1002)
    - 135.0196A Edge number note, undated; 152797 (Box 23, Folder 1003)
    - 135.0197A Edge number note, undated; 152796 (Box 23, Folder 1004)
    - 135.0198A Edge number note, undated; 152795 (Box 23, Folder 1005)
    - 135.0199A Edge number note, undated; 152794 (Box 23, Folder 1006)
    - 135.0199A-135.0202A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152793 (Box 23, Folder 1007)
    - 135.0200A Edge number note, undated; 152792 (Box 23, Folder 1008)
    - 135.0201A Edge number note, undated; 152791 (Box 23, Folder 1009)
    - 135.0202A Edge number note, undated; 152790 (Box 23, Folder 1010)
    - 135.0203A Edge number note, undated; 152789 (Box 23, Folder 1011)
    - 135.0203A-135.0206A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152788 (Box 23, Folder 1012)
    - 135.0204A Edge number note, undated; 152787 (Box 23, Folder 1013)
    - 135.0205A Edge number note, undated; 152786 (Box 23, Folder 1014)
    - 135.0206A Edge number note, undated; 152785 (Box 23, Folder 1015)
    - 135.0209A Edge number note, undated; 152784 (Box 23, Folder 1016)
    - 135.0209A-135.0214A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152783 (Box 23, Folder 1017)
    - 135.0210A Edge bumber note, undated; 152782 (Box 23, Folder 1018)
    - 135.0211A Edge number note, undated; 152781 (Box 23, Folder 1019)
    - 135.0212A Edge number note, undated; 152780 (Box 23, Folder 1020)
    - 135.0213A Edge number note, undated; 152779 (Box 23, Folder 1021)
    - 135.0214A Edge number note, undated; 152778 (Box 23, Folder 1022)
    - 135.0215A Edge number note, undated; 152777 (Box 23, Folder 1023)
    - 135.0215A-135.0220A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987; 152776 (Box 23, Folder 1024)
    - 135.0216A Edge number note, undated; 152775 (Box 23, Folder 1025)
    - 135.0217A Edge number note, undated; 152774 (Box 23, Folder 1026)
    - 135.0218A Edge number note, undated; 152773 (Box 23, Folder 1027)
    - 135.0219A Edge number note, undated; 152772 (Box 23, Folder 1028)
    - 135.0220A Edge number note, undated; 152771 (Box 23, Folder 1029)
    - 135.0240A Timer's listing, 1987; 152770 (Box 23, Folder 1030)
    - 135.0242A Timer's Listing, 1987; 152769 (Box 23, Folder 1031)
    - 135.0423A-135.0244A timer's listing, 1987; 152768 (Box 23, Folder 1032)
  - Subseries C: Production materials, 152728
    - Auditor's report, 1985; 152766 (Box 23, Folder 1033)
    - Biographical information, Frank Moore and Jim Self, undated; 152765 (Box 23, Folder 1034)
    - Budgets, 1985-1987; 152764 (Box 23, Folder 1035)
    - Camera Reports, ca. 1987; 152763 (Box 23, Folder 1036)
    - Camera shot list and filming notes, undated; 152762 (Box 23, Folder 1037)
    - Correspondence, undated; 152761 (Box 23, Folder 1038)
    - Currency exchange, 1987; 152760 (Box 23, Folder 1039)
    - Dialogue scripts, undated; 152759 (Box 25, Folder 1040)
    - DuArt film laboratories, 1985-1987; 152758 (Box 25, Folder 1041)
    - Fabric, undated; 152757 (Box 25, Folder 1042)
    - Film and Video Arts, 1986-1987; 152756 (Box 25, Folder 1043)
    - Grant applications, miscellaneous and partial., 1986; 152755 (Box 25, Folder 1044)
    - Insurance, undated; 152754 (Box 25, Folder 1045)
    - Lighting, undated; 152753 (Box 25, Folder 1046)
    - Mother's Sound Stages, 1987; 152752 (Box 25, Folder 1047)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1987; 152751 (Box 25, Folder 1048)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1986-1987; 152750 (Box 25, Folder 1049)
    - Notes and miscellaneous papers, undated; 152749 (Box 25, Folder 1050)
    - Payroll, undated; 152748 (Box 25, Folder 1051)
    - phone lists, undated; 152747 (Box 25, Folder 1052)
    - Photographs, taken during production, undated; 152746 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_5c2c36bab5d9cf636fd0237a70f6655a)
    - Primary Performance Group general lEdger, account lists, 1987; 152745 (Box 25, Folder 1053)
    - Principal Credits, undated; 152744 (Box 25, Folder 1054)
    - Production Budget worksheet, undated; 152743 (Box 25, Folder 1055)
    - Production/rehearsal schedules, undated; 152742 (Box 25, Folder 1056)
    - Provost Displays, undated; 152741 (Box 25, Folder 1057)
    - PS 1 proposal, 1987; 152740 (Box 25, Folder 1058)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204568 (Box 25, Folder 1059)
    - Receipts, 1987; 152739 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
    - Rental notes, undated; 152738 (Box 25, Folder 1061)
    - Scene breakdown, undated; 152737 (Box 25, Folder 1062)
    - Sketches, undated; 152736 (Box 25, Folder 1063)
    - Storyboard, complete, undated; 152735 (Box 25, Folder 1064)
    - Storyboard fragments and copies, undated; 152734 (Box 25, Folder 1065)
    - Summary of The Miller's Wife, undated; 152733 (Box 25, Folder 1066)
    - Tax exemption paperwork, 1983; 152732 (Box 25, Folder 1067)
    - Time Chart, undated; 152731 (Box 25, Folder 1068)
    - Titles, drawn by Frank Moore, undated; 152730 (Box 25, Folder 1069)
    - WNET/Media Alliance. On-Line program application, undated; 152729 (Box 25, Folder 1070)
  - Subseries D: Promotional Materials, 152725
    - Photographic stills, undated; 152727 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_0b0cf2912f83332e68fc4ba1d488fb2c)
    - Postcard invitations, undated; 152726 (Box 25, Folder 1071)
  - Subseries E: Artifacts, 152723
    - broken glass, undated; 152724 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_468a96dc70fba15c0d2198bbbdcd3d19)
  - Subseries F: Video Recordings - Access Copies, 152722
    - The Millers Wife - Work Sample (Master), [1987]; ID: 135.0292; 255047 (Case 135.0292)
      TRT: 00:04:30
      Source ID: 135.0256
    - The Miller's Wife - Work Sample, [1987]; ID: 135.0280; 213978 (Case 135.0280)
      Source ID: 135.0257
    - The Miller's Wife - Scratchtrack Master, [1987]; ID: 135.0290; 255048 (Case 135.0290)
      TRT: 00:25:00
      Source ID: 135.0173
    - The Miller's Wife (w/ Scratchtrack), [1987]; ID: 135.0281; 213979 (Case 135.0281)
      Source ID: 135.0170
    - The Miller's Wife - Master of Roughcut, Silent, [1987]; ID: 135.0289; 255049 (Case 135.0289)
      Source ID: 135.0172
    - The Miller's Wife - Silent Workprint, [1987]; ID: 135.0286; 218767 (Case 135.0286)
      TRT: Approx.00:30:00
      Source ID: 135.0169
    - The Miller's Wife - (Work in Progress) from 16mm Print, [1987]; ID: 135.0291; 255050 (Case 135.0291)
      Original Format: Umatic
      Source ID: 135.0255
  - Subseries G: Film - Access Copies, 152721
    Films have not been preserved and are not available for research.
- Series VII: Additional Moving Image and Sound Recordings, 152706
  Series VII contains media materials unrelated to either Beehive or The Miller's Wife. Subseries A contains the media materials themselves and subseries B contains production information.
  - Subseries A: Video and Sound Recordings - Access Copies, 152719
    - The Boogieman/ Aquaman-- Studies for a Work in Progress, Moore/ Self, undated; ID: 135.0282; 213980 (Case 135.0282)
      TRT: 00:05:00
      Source ID: 135.0265
    - Crankhouse, DTW, 6/1/1988-- Frank Moore/ Jim Self, ID: 135.0283; 213981 (Case 135.0283)
      TRT: 00:57:00
      Source ID: 135.0262
    - Ruban Rouge, undated; ID: 135.0284; 213982 (Case 135.0284)
      TRT: 00:01:40
      Source ID: 135.0267
    - A Tribute to Frank Moore, a Film by Rebecca Moore and Denise Zmekhol, Undated; ID: 135.0293; 255046 (Case 135.0293, Case 135.0294)
      TRT: 00:12:00
      Also available on Blu-Ray Disc - ID: 135.0294
  - Subseries B: Video and Sound Recordings and Motion Picture Film - Originals, 152710
    Subseries B contains all original material. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A. Please see Fales Archivist.
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - "Crankhouse" [2 versions]; approx. 00:53:00 min.; appears to be 2 versions of "Crankhouse", (1)-30 minutes (2)-23 minutes. Both taped at Dance Theater Workshop, June 1, 1988., 152718 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0261)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Fuji 60-min. videocassette
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - "Crankhouse" Dance Theater Workshop (DTW) June 1, 1988., 152717 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0262)
      Videorecording, VHS, Kodak T-120 videocassette.
    - Jim Self / Frank Moore - Primary Performance Group, Three Excerpts: (1) Tuscaloosa, (2) Camellia, (3) Beehive [Master tape]., undated; 152716 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0263)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Kodak KCS 20-EB 930 videocassette.
    - Jim Self and Dancers, "Excerpts 1981"., 152715 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0264)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Scotch videocassette.
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - The Boogieman, Aquaman: Studies for a work in progress, 6 minutes, silent., undated; 152714 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0265)
      Videorecording, VHS, EK T-30 videocassette.
    - PG Interview, 21 August 1985., 152713 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0266)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, UCA 20s videocassette.
    - Ruban Rouge., undated; 152712 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0267)
      Videorecording, VHS Maxell T-120 P/I Plus videocassette.
    - Shaman-Mattox July, 1984. Side A: (1) Charlie, (2) Shaman-I (early version, Bob Weir- Shamanic voices, George Marsh- congas, cymbals), (3) Shaman-II synthesis only. Side B: (1) Shaman-III (Mel Graves-Bass), (2) Shaman-IV (excerpt from opening- Bob Ernst- voice of death.), 152711 (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0268)
      Audiorecording, Pacific Stereo 90-minute audiocassette.
    - Undeveloped motion picture film, 1987; 277178; 7 media elements Seven rolls of 16mm film, undeveloped.
    - Beehive, digital audio tape (Box PM 38, Case 135.0276)
    - Whitney Biennial, undated (Box 70, Vhs 135.0261)
    - Self/Moore (Video: Christine Tyrnell), 1988-07-22 (Box 70, Vhs 135.0262)
    - Robert Neal Fulps In Memorium, April 1991 (Box 70, Vhs 135.0266)
    - Frank Moore Memorial Audiocassette, 2002 (Box 70, Audiocassette 135.0267)
  - Subseries C: Production Information, 152707
    - Blue Grotto, undated; 152709 (Box 25, Folder 1072)
    - Camellia. Notes regarding the rights and reproduction of the piece as well as a draft of the agreement with Dick Connette, undated; 152708 (Box 25, Folder 1073)
- Series VIII: Artifacts and Objects, 152674
  This series contains artifacts and objects relating to Frank Moore's life and artwork. The series is divided into three subseries. Subseries A: Personal artifacts includes objects such as x-rays. Subseries B: Art Implements and Artifacts includes materials such as paint brushes. Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes objects such as the original AIDS ribbons. This series is organized alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Personal Items, 152701
    - Item removed to oversize, 204564 (Box 25, Folder 1074)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204565 (Box 25, Folder 1075)
    - X-Rays and report. Chest and lungs. American Hospital of Paris. November-December 1977 and January 1978 [additional materials in oversize box], 1977-1978; 152705 (Box 25, Folder 1076)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204566 (Box 25, Folder 1077)
    - Item removed to oversize, 204567 (Box 25, Folder 1078)